Guide to the Irving J. Lewis Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Inventory, 1960s-1980s, undated; 12 linear feet (12 boxes)
  - Washington files, Late 1960s-1970s, undated (Box 11)
    - Budget
      - 5-Year Plan (Box 11)
      - '72 Budget (Box 11)
    - Alcoholism case study (Box 11)
    - American Hospital Association (AHA) (Box 11)
    - American Medical Association (AMA) (Box 11)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges (AAMA) (Box 11)
    - Biomedical research (Box 11)
    - Case studies (Box 11)
    - Community health -- medical education (Box 11)
    - Community health planning (Box 11)
    - Community pathological conference (Box 11)
    - Comprehensive health planning (Box 11)
    - CHP/RMP (Box 11)
    - Consumers (Box 11)
    - Curriculum (Box 11)
    - Decentralization (Box 11)
    - Development of federal health policy (Box 11)
    - Environmental Protection Agency - reorganization (Box 11)
    - Erosion of agency head (Box 11)
    - Family Assistance Act (Box 11)
    - Family planning guidelines (Box 11)
    - Federal health policy (Box 11)
    - Federal policy for social affairs (Box 11)
    - Federalism (Box 11)
    - Health block grant (314 d) (Box 11)
    - Health financing/health services (Box 11)
    - Health organization (Box 11)
    - Health planning (Box 11)
    - Health security program (Box 11)
    - Health services project grants (Box 11)
    - HEW Model cities funding - FY '71 (Box 11)
    - Hospital financing - planning (Box 11)
    - Hospitals- Hill/Burton (Box 11)
    - Hospital reimbursement (Box 11)
    - HSMHA organization (Box 11)
    - Kaiser Permanente (Box 12)
    - Key people (Box 12)
    - Kiddicare (Box 12)
    - Little, A. D. (Box 12)
    - Manpower (Box 12)
    - Martin Luther King Center (Box 12)
    - MIT - Irving London (Box 12)
    - Medical education (Box 12)
    - Medicare/Medicaid (Box 12)
    - Mental health insurance and Medicaid (Box 12)
    - Migrant health (Box 12)
    - National Center for Health Services Research and Development (Box 12)
    - National health insurance (Box 12)
    - Nutrition (Box 12)
    - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO) Centers (Box 12)
    - Office of Management and Budget (Box 12)
    - Organization and delivery (Box 12)
    - Piel Commission Report (Box 12)
    - Politics and the Ghettos (Box 12)
    - Planning, Programming, Budgeting (PPB) material from Bureau of Budget - 1968 (Box 12)
    - PPB - General (Box 12)
    - Public Health Service (PHS) Hospitals (Box 12)
    - Regional Medical Programs (RMP) - General (Box 12)
    - RMP Conference - Airlie House, 1969 September 27-29 (Box 12)
    - RMP - Community health (Box 12)
    - Role of state government in medical care (Box 12)
    - Secretary Richardson's speeches (Box 12)
    - Selected Health System Project proposals (Box 12)
    - Shannon's analysis of health (Box 12)
    - Social goals - objectives - poverty (Box 12)
    - Social Policy in Health (Box 12)
    - Social Policy in Sweden (Box 12)
    - Social Security - Constitutional law (Box 12)
    - Social Security financing (Box 12)
    - Student health activities (Box 12)
    - Study of Cost and Financing of Heart Transplantation (Box 12)
    - TB control (Box 12)
    - Urban Coalition (Box 12)
    - VA - Long-range plan (Box 12)
    - White House Conference on Health - 1st meeting (Box 12)
    - White House Conference on Health - 2nd meeting (Box 12)